(August 2026)
(The teaser of My Genie Secretary was revealed.)
(My Genie Secretary)
(A lot of fans who had been waiting for Season 2 left comments.)
(The artist most recommended to be My Star)
(- Please invite RESCENE. - RESCENE on My Genie Secretary.)
(- RESCENE, please. - I hope RESCENE comes.)
(I'm looking forward to seeing you guys become RESCENE's managers.)
(Take care of RESCENE!)
(The stars everyone wanted to see)
(Their wishes will be granted now.)
(The studio in Yeonhui-dong here My Star is waiting)
(Both secretaries came at the same time.)
Isn't it cute?
I got this in a hurry...
for the babies.
- What did you get? - The T-shirt.
The babies are coming today.
I should wear something appropriate.
(Today's My Star is young.)
Look at this. The babies will love it...
when they see Donald Duck.
- That's not Donald Duck. - What?
What's its name?
- Tweety. - It's Tweety.
- It's not Donald. - It's not?
Donald looks like this.
- They're similar. - Gosh.
Have you memorized all of their names yet?
(Today, we have 5 My Stars.)
What are their names?
- Woni. - Yes.
Minami.
- May, Liv, and Zena. - Yes.
Okay.
- I studied last night. - You studied a lot.
- I studied a lot. - You did?
(My Stars, who went from a dirt stage at an elementary school...)
(to performing in front of 60,000 people at a stadium)
(From dirt to Sangam, their story is incredibly moving.)
("LOVE ATTACK," released in 2024, recently went viral.)
(Number 1 on the music charts for 9 consecutive weeks)
("RESCENE Takes Number 1 in Singer Brand Reputation")
(RESCENE, the best rising star in 2026)
We don't know much about them.
We don't know.
Right? Do you know them?
You've never heard of them, have you?
I knew something about Geoje.
- Right. - But I studied yesterday.
You only heard their names for the first time yesterday.
- That's right. - I told you.
They get around 100 booking calls a day.
They can't even get any work done because they're busy taking calls.
Good for them.
(Secretly jealous)
And...
they have 40 engagements scheduled in a week.
(Including a lemon-lime soda commercial,)
(they got over 100 advertising offers.)
(An average of 40 schedules a week)
They came back from LA yesterday.
All of them?
They've barely been getting any sleep lately.
Don't all successful idols their age...
barely get any sleep?
They should sleep on the plane.
Don't you feel bad for them?
That's just how it is.
They should get some sleep on the plane.
As their secretary,
you need to make sure they have enough energy for today.
How?
They should take care of us.
They're so young.
This man is about to collapse.
- Gosh. - Right?
That's a good idea.
- Yes. They should take care of us. - I mean,
they're so young.
Nice.
(My Stars are doing a photoshoot for a commercial.)
(As one of the hottest acts in the industry right now,)
(they're showing how professional they are.)
(Hurry up, secretary uncles!)
(The secretaries enter the studio to get briefed on the job.)
Hello.
- Are you the manager? - Yes.
- I'm Kim Ye Jin, RESCENE's manager. - I see.
- Thank you for coming. - Hello.
- Hello. - Here.
Today's to-do list.
The members...
will be doing a photoshoot for a commercial.
(A photoshoot for a commercial)
They'll film a YouTube video for the "HIAW" channel.
(HIAW?)
- What's HIAW? - For the "HIAW" channel.
It's Woni's personal YouTube channel.
"Hello, I Am Woni,"
- "Nice to Meet You." - "Nice to Meet You?"
Geoje, yaho!
(From the legendary "Geoje, yaho...")
(to countless viral memes)
(14.3 million views)
(13.27 million views)
(12.57 million views)
(11.77 million views)
(Surpassing 400 million total views)
(After uploading their 1st video in February 2026,)
(their subscriber count skyrocketed just 3 months later...)
(thanks to a breakout video.)
(Hello, I Am Woni, Nice to Meet You, 2.22 million subscribers)
(They reached 2.22 million subscribers...)
(just 7 months after launching the channel.)
Do you really have to shorten it that way?
Everyone calls it "HIAW."
(The oldie isn't happy about the abbreviation.)
Their average age is 20.6.
(Please take care of them in a way that resonates with Gen Z!)
Please take care of them in a way that resonates with Gen Z.
Not even 26.
(My Stars' average age is 20.6.)
We're not that much older...
than 20.6.
Even if you add 30 to their average age, they'd still be younger.
(Even if you add 30 to their age, they'd still be younger than us.)
(What are you talking about?)
(Liv, 19 years old, May, 18 years old)
(Zena, 17 years old, Woni, 22 years old)
(Minami, 19 years old)
(The youngest My Stars, with an average age of 20.6)
Can you please write their parents' age...
instead of theirs?
Even their parents might be younger than us.
Their parents...
- They must be young. - must be young too.
What have we been doing all this time?
Don't drag me into this.
- Our encounter - Don't lump me in with you.
(Let me relate us by age, at least.)
Food is very important...
- Food? - to them.
They love Korean food.
They like gukbap and stuff.
They often want different dishes.
So please get each of them the food they want.
Are you already catering to all of their individual preferences?
(Are you already catering to all of their individual preferences?)
Already? They're all successful now, right?
To the point where you have to cater to them?
Food is important. They need to eat to get energy.
- So they don't just eat anything. - Sorry?
You have to cater to their individual preferences?
(That's not what it is.)
Don't worry. He's a gukbap expert.
(He might complain, but he'll make sure they eat.)
When they...
start getting tired during filming,
they like it when you compliment them or say things like this.
"You can do this. Can't you even do something like this?"
They already need to hear those words?
They're no different from Seo In Young.
(Their former My Star required a lot of attention.)
They're just like her.
Do they like to be called Princess too?
Zena is known as Princess of Silla.
She loves to be called Princess.
- If you adore her... - We have a princess every week.
- and call her Princess... - We have a princess every week.
(The complainer finally snaps.)
My goodness.
These are the items we always carry around when we have a schedule.
(It's time to hand over the bag.)
We always carry this around.
It reminds me of the bag for ALLDAY PROJECT.
They're sensitive to the cold.
Please make sure they have these blankets while they're waiting.
They often sweat when they dance.
So I carry around a separate pouch for electric fans.
Put water bottles here...
and give it to them when they need it.
Their names are written here.
(There are name stickers on it.)
They need to take breaks every now and then,
so we carry a mat around for them.
(A mat?)
When they want to take a break,
please put this mat on the floor. They'll be lying there.
Good night.
(An essential item for My Stars who can't get enough sleep)
(They catch up on sleep with short naps.)
They'll be lying there.
They lie down while everyone is working?
Even I don't do that.
(Here comes Seo Jin, the Thinker, again.)
Even I don't lie down just because I'm tired.
- They're very busy. - It's for short naps.
What's really better? Taking a quick nap between schedules,
or taking a nap at home because you have no work?
(Seo Jin is right.)
You shouldn't feel bad for them. That's a good thing.
It's because they're popular.
If they don't have work, they'll order jjajangmyeon at home,
waiting for their next job. That's not a good thing.
You're right.
You're Team RESCENE today.
So I got T-shirts for you.
- Do you want us to wear it? - Yes. Please make sure to wear it.
Why does everyone give us clothes these days?
All the staff members on set are wearing this T-shirt.
Put it on.
(Yaho T-shirts featuring My Stars' photo)
(These shirts were prepared by the ad production team.)
Everyone is wearing it.
(Staring)
What's "Yaho?" What's "RESCENE yaho?"
What is it? Is it a chant?
(He has a long way to go.)
(The meeting between My Stars, with an average age of 20.6,)
(and the secretaries, with an average age of 56.5)
(She wants to add fen hao zi.)
(What's fen hao zi?)
(It's a wax squishy.)
(What's a wax squishy?)
(Do you know any abbreviations?)
(I hate abbreviations.)
(If you make a lot of money, happiness will follow.)
(But is money really everything?)
(It's everything. Money is everything.)
(It's just a generation gap.)
(20.6 versus 56.5)
(With the biggest age gap ever, can they make it work?)
They're over there.
- My gosh. - They're over there.
(They're going to meet the secretaries now.)
It feels like I'm meeting celebrities.
(Geoje Girl, Woni)
Here they are.
- Hello. - Hello.
- Hello. - Come on in.
(Smiling like a dad)
Come on in, everyone.
Hello.
(My Star, RESCENE)
- Hello. - Yaho.
- Yaho. - Yaho.
- Hello. - Hello.
One person is missing. Aren't there five of you?
She's doing a photoshoot.
So you know there are five of us.
- Gosh. - Of course, I do.
We even memorized your names.
(Confident)
Do you know their names?
Of course. Let me see if I can match your faces to your names.
Go on.
(Will he be able to match their faces to their names?)
- Woni is so famous. - Who's Woni?
- Woni. - Thank you.
Geoje Woni?
Woni.
I keep getting these two mixed up.
Zena...
I think it's because she has bangs today.
It's because of a different hairstyle and makeup.
One of us is Japanese.
We'll each say a sentence in Japanese.
This is hard.
(Which 1 of the 3 is Minami?)
(The first obstacle)
- Let's say, "Yaho." - Yaho.
Yaho.
(Which one is Minami?)
(Super focused)
Yaho.
(Laughing)
(Embarrassed)
- You don't have to say it. - She's definitely not the one.
- Hey. - She's not Japanese.
- It's 1 of these 2. - Yes.
- Minami? - One of them is Minami.
Which one?
- You guys look alike. - People say they look alike.
You guys look alike. You guys are like twins.
- They look alike. - I'm offended.
Hey.
- I look a bit different, don't I? - Yes. You look very different.
- Right? - You're definitely Korean.
I'm May.
- May? - Yes.
- The shortest one. - No.
It's because I'm the only one with short hair.
So which one is Minami?
- I think... - Which one is Minami?
you're Minami...
- because you have a nasal voice. - Do you think she's Minami?
- You're right. - Correct!
(Minami, a Japanese member)
- You're right. - Your Korean is amazing.
What does your father do?
- Your Japanese is good. - No.
He practiced it yesterday.
- He's usually not this fluent. - Right.
I heard one of you had said my famous line.
I taught Minami.
- I did well, right? - You did?
What does your father do?
So it was you.
- It was me. - I see.
"So it was you."
- He sounds like my dad. - She speaks better Korean than...
- Then who do you think she is? - Zena.
Zena.
- I'm Liv. - She's Liv.
I'm sorry.
(He made a big mistake.)
I don't think I can film today.
No.
- You can't film today? - Hey.
You think you're big shots now. You can't really say that.
I'm sorry I didn't recognize you.
"I don't think I can film today."
You don't get to say that until you're at least three years in.
We're exactly three years in.
You are?
(He ended up going nowhere.)
Today,
there's something you have to do as our managers.
What is it?
You should shout, "Yaho."
What's that?
(What's "Yaho?")
- "Yaho." - It's on your T-shirt.
- "RESCENE, Yaho." - Why "Yaho?"
That's our greeting.
- We just say that. - It's something you say...
- on top of a mountain. - That's different.
- It feels different. - Is it Japanese?
Yes. It's Japanese.
What does "Yaho" mean in Japanese?
It's something you say to greet friends...
- So it's like "Hi?" - or people you're close to.
- That's basically what it is. - It's like "Hi."
How do you say it?
When I say, "RESCENE,"
make this sign, extend your arm,
- and say, "Yaho." - Yaho.
With a nasal voice.
Extend your arm.
(Extend?)
Should I say, "My Genie Secretary?"
- My Genie Secretary, yaho. - Yaho.
- Yaho. - Yaho.
Naho.
(Rolling his eyes back)
You don't have to roll your eyes back.
- I don't? - It's fine.
Why did you roll your eyes back?
(He couldn't hide his girly side.)
RESCENE, are you okay?
- I'm okay. - I'm okay.
I'm okay.
- Let's go. - My Genie Secretary.
- Yaho. - Yaho.
(Watching from the front row)
What does your father do?
- It's something like this. - That's nice.
(He's been saying this phrase for 25 years.)
Thank you.
I guess she's done.
- There's a princess among us. - Where is she?
- Please give her special treatment. - Come on in.
Hello.
Zena.
- Princess. - Hello.
Our princess is here.
- That's our princess. - Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm...
Zena.
Is she from Gyeongju?
- Yes. - She is.
- Princess of Silla? - Princess.
These two are the youngest.
And these 2 were born in 2006.
(Zena and May, the youngest, Minami and Liv, born in 2006)
- And... - She's the eldest.
- She was born in 2004. - I'm the eldest one.
(Woni, the eldest one born in 2004)
So you were born in 2004?
- And you were born in 2005? - We were born in 2008.
- In 2008. - In 2008?
Yes. Both of us.
Don't you have to go to school then?
- They should. - We're 19.
- Are you a 12th grader? - Yes.
(Zena and May, 19 years old and the youngest among them)
You can't wear heavy makeup when you're in 12th grade.
You can't.
If you're in 12th grade,
you should study hard.
What does your father do?
- He's the one who said the phrase. - I can't believe I heard it.
How old are your fathers?
My father was born in 1977.
My goodness.
(The one who was born in 1967 is getting a headache.)
What year were you born in?
- What? - He's ten years older.
- Ten years? - Ten years older than her father.
(Everyone is shocked.)
I should never take off my hat today.
(Showing his bald head)
Please.
(Cheering)
(My Stars' bright and bubbly reaction)
Amazing.
I wanted to see it.
(Uncle is feeling great.)
Hello.
They liked it when you took off your hat.
(Is he jealous?)
- They did? - Yes.
- Take it off. - Whenever you feel down,
I'll take off my hat.
Sounds great.
When did you start learning Korean? How did you get so good at it?
- I... - Your Korean is better than ours.
- Seriously. - She speaks the best Korean.
- I came to Korea a long time ago. - Sorry?
- When did you start learning it? - It's been around five years.
You can't be this good after only five years of learning it.
She's better than us.
I learned Korean while spending time with the members as a trainee.
Isn't her Korean better than Nichkhun's?
Why would you mention him?
I mean, he's not Korean either.
I think she speaks better Korean than he does.
(She mastered Korean just in 5 years.)
- She can speak English too. - She can?
I like learning languages.
- You do? - Yes.
She speaks every language better than you do.
- Why would you attack me? - What?
(He's fluent in 0 languages.)
That's true, though.
How much do you know about us?
Have you heard of us before today?
Yes. I heard of you yesterday.
Yesterday?
I mean, your YouTube videos got tons of views.
- On Woni's channel. - Woni's channel.
- It's her individual channel. - At first...
- There's a story. - That's what I heard.
We're from a small company.
I saw something like that.
- Yes, so... - Yes.
we had nothing at first.
The CEO collected each member.
That's how we got together.
We thought...
we'd get to perform once we debuted.
We thought it was a given.
We debuted,
but we were from such a small company,
so we didn't have a chance to perform even though we wanted to.
- You didn't have a chance? - We released a song,
but we couldn't perform on music shows.
So...
(In reality, they didn't even have a chance to perform.)
That's why...
we decided to do anything.
We couldn't afford to be picky about the size of the event.
We felt grateful...
just to be invited anywhere.
So we even performed at an elementary school sports day.
- An elementary school sports day? - And...
Yes, we went there.
We went to a community center.
We performed for some seniors...
- For some seniors. - outside a community center.
It seemed they didn't know our song, so we sang some trot songs too.
We worked really hard.
- To promote your song? - Yes.
After that,
we found out the response to the channel we're running now...
has been pretty good.
- On YouTube? - Yes.
The fans love it.
"Yaho" definitely played a big part.
- It was the beginning. - Yes.
After she said, "Yaho,"
our channel went viral.
(Geoje, yaho!)
(It was the phrase that made them known to the world.)
(Busan, yaho.)
(With global stars joining the trend,)
("Yaho" became a meme embraced by Koreans everywhere.)
A lot of people got to know us because of that phrase.
- That's what happened? - Yes.
Thanks to your YouTube channel?
People discovered our performances...
and recognized how hard we'd worked.
I think that's why they like us.
(Their journey of growth captivated the public.)
- I saw your videos. - You did?
- Really? - Thank you.
Each of us...
Yaho. I saw it.
So today, you'll be working as our managers.
- Do you need anything? - We...
We need a lot of things. We always call our managers...
by their nicknames.
- Right. - They all have nicknames.
- They do? - So...
if we just called by your formal title,
we might not feel comfortable saying what we want to say.
- Right. - That's true.
- So you want to give us nicknames. - We need to come up with it.
- We need to come up with it. - Like what?
For example, Kkyu.
(Kkyu)
- "Kkyu" sounds good. - "Kkyu" sounds good.
- He likes that nickname. - Kkyu.
- Kkyu, yaho. - Kkyu.
Or how about this?
Kkyu and Jjyu.
- Kkyu-Jjyu. - Kkyu-Jjyu?
- Yes. Kkyu and Jjyu. - Why Jjyu?
- What's Jjyu? - Because his name is Seo Jin.
- Jjyu? - It's the J.
- Jjyu? - "It's the J."
- My gosh. - His name has a J in it, so Jjyu?
- It sounds good. - It sounds like a dog name.
- Jjyu. - Jjyu.
That's what you say when you call a dog.
(Today's secretaries are Kkyu and Jjyu.)
So what are we doing here today?
- It's a commercial. - It's a commercial.
You should keep checking on us.
Make sure we eat properly.
- I'm hungry. - Food is very important.
I'm starving.
Since we're doing a group shoot soon,
- should we order food in advance? - Let's do that.
- What do you want? - Great.
- It's a brilliant idea. - What do you want?
- Are you a genius? - Can you...
- Kkyu-Jjyu. - Kkyu-Jjyu.
We want to eat malatang.
- Malatang. - Malatang?
- Malatang! - No, you'll gain weight.
Why not?
(Kkyu surprisingly gave a cold refusal.)
We'll resume the photoshoot. I'm sorry.
- Okay. - Is it a group shoot now?
Yes.
Who wants to eat malatang?
(He quickly takes orders before the photoshoot.)
Do you just want malatang?
I want to eat seolleongtang.
- Then... - Are you really from Japan?
I'll join you then.
- Do you want seolleongtang too? - Yes.
So 2 bowls of seolleongtang and 2 bowls of malatang?
- Yes. That's perfect. - Is that all you need?
- Please add fen hao zi. - Sorry?
Please add fen hao zi.
- To the malatang. - What's fen hao zi?
Don't you know what it is?
- Is it for malatang? - Yes.
- Glass noodles too. - Fen hao zi.
Fan hao zi?
Is it "fan" or "fen?"
- Fen. - Fen hao zi?
"Fen hao zi."
(He doesn't know what it is, but he writes it down.)
So what do you want to add?
Fen hao zi.
Fen hao zi...
- and mung bean sprouts. - Mung bean sprouts?
Kwang Kyu, please add that.
- But the basic ingredients are... - There are...
a lot of basic ingredients.
- You should add them all. - Mung bean sprouts?
- Yes. - Gosh. Kwang Kyu.
Mung bean sprouts?
Tell us everything.
- It'd be better to check. - Yes.
- Let us add it. - Fen hao zi, mung bean sprouts.
- Let us add it. - Not seolleongtang.
- Yes. - Two servings of malatang?
- Yes. - Isn't two servings a bit much?
- It's 2 servings, level 1.5. - It's okay.
- Is it the spiciness level? - Is it the spiciness level?
Yes.
- So they have different levels. - Let's add more.
- Wood ear. - And cabbage.
Do you eat wood ear too?
Cabbage.
- Cabbage? - Wood ear.
(Laughing in disbelief)
Dried tofu.
- Dried tofu. - You guys will gain weight.
- Dried tofu? - You guys eat a lot.
Potato.
- Really? - Your company treats you guys well.
Cheesy rice cake?
(The Japanese member is taking notes.)
(Mung bean sprouts, cabbage, wood ear mushroom, enoki mushroom,)
(dried tofu, Chinese glass noodles)
- Yes. - Can you fit...
all these ingredients into two servings?
- That's... - And...
- Snow ear. - Small napa cabbage.
Chinese glass noodles.
(It's a new world to him.)
Can we begin the photoshoot now?
- Yes. - Yes.
- Hurry up and go. - Let's go.
- Go now. - Put on your shoes.
It's fine. We should...
- I caught a cold. - Okay.
Can you give me some medicine after I eat?
- Sure. - We have cold medicine.
- All right. - Are you done?
- Thank you. - Is everything okay?
- Okay. - Let's go.
(Their first task is to prepare lunch.)
Will all these ingredients fit into two servings?
- What? - Will these fit into two servings?
(Malatang with 12 ingredients)
- Two bowls of seolleongtang? - Yes.
"Fen hao zi malatang." Is this what they were talking about?
"Fen..."
What's fen hao zi?
"Fen hao zi."
- It's fen hao zi malatang, right? - Yes.
That's what they wanted.
Didn't they tell us to add fen hao zi to their malatang?
(Confused)
They wanted to order fen hao zi malatang.
I don't know.
(I have no idea.)
I should look up what "fen hao zi" is.
(He looks up what "fen hao zi" is before ordering delivery.)
This is fen hao zi.
- It's like rice cake. - I added it.
You did?
I thought fen hao zi was like the hat I wear.
"Hao zi" sounds like "hat" in Korean.
Mung bean sprouts? Should we add them?
Yes. They wanted mung bean sprouts.
Small napa cabbage, Chinese glass noodles.
- How about tofu? - Tofu?
Dried tofu.
- Dried tofu? - Yes.
Did you add Chinese glass noodles?
"Chinese wide glass noodles?"
(They're adding ingredients even though they're a bit slow.)
Are wood ear and snow ear different?
They wrote both.
"Wood ear, snow ear."
- It says "black wood ear." - What?
- Black wood ear. - "Black wood ear?"
- Should we add black wood ear? - What's that?
Should we add both black wood ear and snow ear?
(Adding black wood ear and snow ear)
Why are there so many ingredients?
- There's a lot. - Why?
"A lot of zhi ma jiang?" Did they write anything about it?
No.
First off...
What are "corn noodles?"
(Should we go and ask them?)
- Hand the phone to them. - What?
Hand it to them.
Guys, what do you want to do with the zhi ma jiang?
- What? Zhi ma jiang? - Yes.
Just the basics.
- The basics? - Yes.
- Pickled radish? - No, thanks.
- No? - Jjyu.
Can you check how we look?
- You look great. - Well...
You look the best.
(Complimenting them without even looking at them)
- Oh, right. Guo bao rou! - Guo bao rou?
Please order guo bao rou.
I did.
(He orders guo bao rou for them.)
Let's get it started.
(The group shoot begins.)
Nice. Liv, put your hands together. That looks pretty.
Okay.
Okay. Good.
(Liv, May)
Good job.
A little more playfully.
You can get closer.
Playfully.
(They're perfectly in sync, even without saying a word.)
Nice.
(RESCENE shines with the charm of all five members.)
(They nail the photoshoot with ease, like the trending idols they are.)
(They're all doing great.)
(Exclaiming)
It just skyrocketed overnight.
This must feel like a dream right now.
After performing at school fields and local community events,
they suddenly...
At KCON,
it's mainly for international fans.
(My Stars returned from performing at KCON LA.)
It's held in LA.
So many international fans...
filled that huge hall.
(International fans filled the venue.)
Aren't they all overseas Koreans?
- No. - No?
Foreign people.
Overseas Koreans don't come.
- In the past, it was mostly... - Not these days.
Is it "Gayo Stage?"
I guess things have changed a lot.
Overseas Koreans?
Our overseas Koreans.
I want a sip.
- I'm thirsty. - Woni...
No.
Woni.
Should we ask Jjyu-Kkyu?
(Hesitating)
(Glancing)
(My Stars aren't comfortable with the senior secretaries.)
I'm thirsty, Jjyu-Kkyu.
(Gathering up her courage)
Would you like a lemon-lime soda?
Yes, please!
- They want a lemon-lime soda. - What?
They want a lemon-lime soda.
(My Stars worked up the courage to ask for a lemon-lime soda.)
(Even setting up a custom tray)
Put them here.
Even a tray?
(Giggling over even the smallest acts of care)
Jjyu is cute.
He's cute.
This is Woni's.
Liv.
Put the straws.
(Floating)
(All the straws are floating.)
(Taking care of all 5 slows things down.)
Let's begin.
You're late, Jjyu-Kkyu.
I'm sorry.
- We can't give it to them. - First...
Let's have a test shot.
(He waits in front of them.)
Give me a moment.
- Go in there now. - A moment, please.
A moment, please.
They'll just have a sip.
- Straws too. Amazing. - Amazing.
- Even straws. - They even did that?
- Thank you. - You're the best.
- What... - Kkyu.
This is touching.
This is a tip.
(Using the can tab to hold the straw in place)
Amazing.
I'm Korean.
- Where? - I'm Liv.
Where's Liv's name?
- At the back. - Liv.
May.
- May. - The older ones and...
(Taking care of all 5 is more hectic than ever.)
Thank you.
I'm sorry!
(Thank you, Jjyu-Kkyu.)
This is a great tip.
That's how it's supposed to be put?
Right.
There are all kinds of...
(What an unexpected tip.)
Since it keeps floating...
- It doesn't fit. - You have to hold it up a bit.
(Breaking)
You have to hold it up a bit.
Goodness.
(Why do things like this always happen to Kwang Kyu?)
What do I do?
Goodness.
It's floating.
Just remove that.
It can't be helped.
(Picking up more little tricks by the day)
We're done with the group shots.
- We'll move on to individual shots. - Okay.
(Minami stays behind to shoot her individual shots.)
Are we going to have malatang?
Is it not here yet?
Is the malatang here?
It should be here now.
- Should I go check? - It should be at the door.
(Their seolleongtang arrived first.)
- I'm done. - You're done?
- You should eat now. - Well done.
Thank you.
- Well done. - Well done.
(They take turns eating during the individual shoot.)
- Is the food here? - The malatang isn't here yet.
Our food isn't here yet?
It's here.
The malatang isn't here yet.
It's here. Don't worry.
He went to get it.
It's in front of the door.
(May is blinded by the sight of seolleongtang.)
This...
Why are you in such a hurry?
- Let's set up this place. - Okay.
What are we going to do if we become princesses?
Should we wait like princesses?
Yes.
Wait just a minute.
(Kwang Kyu heads to get the malatang.)
Is that malatang?
- Yes. Hello. - Hello.
- Thank you. - I'm a fan.
Thank you.
Thank you. It's a rainy day.
- Hello. - Hello.
- I'm a huge fan. - Really?
Thank you.
Drive safely!
- Thank you. - Bye.
(He returns with both hands full.)
Malatang, yaho!
- Yaho! - Yaho!
Amazing.
He went to get it.
I paid for it.
Did you use your card?
- What? - You paid for it?
Of course. It's always my card.
- Really? - Really?
Send the bill.
(He doesn't know how to register the company card.)
- It's okay. - Thank you for the food.
Had I known, I wouldn't have added Chinese glass noodles.
- Why? - It's for an additional price.
Everything is for an additional price.
- It would have cost 50 dollars. - That's true.
Open them.
What are you doing? Open the lids.
Why are you in such a hurry?
We're so hungry.
- Here. - Thank you.
Thank you.
Goodness.
(Zena joins the malatang table.)
- Amazing. - Come here.
Jjyu used his own card to pay for this.
- He used his own card. - What?
Jjyu is amazing!
- Eat up. - Amazing.
- Thank you for the food. - Thank you for the food.
We'll need some cups to use as plates.
They can use this.
Hey.
(How could you give My Stars lids?)
That's how it's supposed to be used.
- We always use that. - We can use that.
- Everyone does it like this. - Really?
(She's already eating.)
There's so much food.
There's a lot.
The mala flavor is pretty strong.
You're eating well.
(May blows on the seolleongtang to cool it down.)
(She doesn't forget the kkakdugi.)
Which two ordered seolleongtang?
Minami and me.
Minami is shooting.
(I want to eat my seolleongtang quickly.)
What did you say this was?
- Fen hao zi. - So that's fen hao zi?
- Fen hao zi? - Yes.
What's fen hao zi?
That's fen hao zi.
The one that looks like tteokbokki. That's fen hao zi.
(Chewy glass noodles that look like tteokbokki)
What are those noodles?
Corn noodles.
Those are corn noodles?
(The older guys are unfamiliar with today's food trends.)
We're learning a lot.
Eat up.
(A mouthful of black wood ear mushrooms)
Goodness.
- You like mushrooms. - Woni likes mushrooms.
I guess so.
(Zena eats snow ear mushrooms.)
Show us your eating show.
It's...
(May goes for bok choy.)
(Liv goes for flat glass noodles.)
Amazing.
The glass noodles are so huge. They kind of scare me.
(Growling)
(It's scary, isn't it?)
It's scary.
(He'll gladly be scared.)
(He reacts well.)
Glass noodles, yaho.
It's so scary.
(They're enjoying it to the fullest.)
They're eating so much malatang in those outfits.
(The princesses devour the malatang.)
Be careful not to get it on your clothes.
- Okay. - Okay.
That's what our manager says the most.
- Be careful of your clothes. - Your...
Your manager says that?
- Yes. - Yes.
(Yes)
- Have some. Let's eat together. - Let's eat together.
- Do you not like such things? - No.
It's too spicy.
- They wouldn't like it. - It's not spicy.
The mala flavor is strong.
- My father also doesn't like it. - Your father?
What does your father do?
Dad...
- He lives in Hwangseong-dong. - Yes.
- At the broadcasting station? - No.
Hwangseong-dong.
He can't hear so well.
Grandpa has poor hearing.
He'll soon get hearing aids.
(Grandpa Kwang Kyu hears it wrong again.)
We didn't add beef.
Right.
That was your fault.
I didn't do it wrong.
- It's our fault. - Hey.
You didn't tell us.
Isn't beef the most important ingredient in malatang?
- It is. - That's true.
I forgot.
- I'm glad we didn't write it down. - Why?
If we had written it down...
It wouldn't have been there.
- Beef wouldn't have been there. - No beef.
It's not here. I don't see beef.
I can't find it.
Normally, people know that beef is a default.
(Geoje Girl)
Why did they miss that?
(Why did they miss that?)
You didn't mention beef.
But they don't really know malatang well.
Is that also a generational gap?
There's guo bao rou.
Right.
- I should have guo bao rou. - Right.
Have one guo bao rou.
It's not there.
(Sniffling)
It's okay.
It seems too spicy for May.
Me?
It seems too spicy for you. You're sniffling.
- Do you want some lemon-lime soda? - Kkyu.
Get her a lemon-lime soda.
I think she needs some tissues.
- Tissue? - She's got a runny nose.
I guess he could see my nose shine.
Thank you.
(They're taking care of them from both sides.)
Have the seolleongtang. Stop eating that now.
- Stop eating malatang. - No.
No. Malatang tastes too good.
It tastes even better because Jjyu-Kkyu ordered it.
Right.
It's the best malatang I've ever had.
It's good even without meat.
It's been such a long while since we last had this.
Woni and Liv, you're up.
(I just started eating.)
Could you ask them if I can have ten more minutes?
(I want to eat more.)
Come here.
(Minami is back from her individual shoot.)
Start eating.
- Just eat first. - Woni and Liv have to go.
Keep eating.
- Uncle told us to eat. - Yes. Eat first.
- Okay. - They have to set up.
I have to go first.
Did you eat enough? Are you crying as well?
- It's delicious. - Why did you eat such spicy food...
when you were going to cry so much?
(Liv heads to get changed.)
This is really good.
What do you want, Minami?
- Seolleongtang. - I want seolleongtang.
Seolleongtang for Minami.
That looks good.
Thank you.
There's salt too.
(Sprinkling)
- Do you want rice as well? - Yes, please.
The noodles are amazing.
(She even adds noodles.)
I'm going to take off my rings.
I'm going to have a proper meal.
(Staring)
The rings. Kwang Kyu!
Put them on Kkyu's fingers.
- Kkyu! - It's his lifelong dream...
to wear a ring.
(Come, rings.)
Kkyu.
- Will they fit? - Kkyu.
(Too tight)
They don't fit.
- Kkyu. - Just push them.
(Just give it to me first.)
(His lifelong dream comes true.)
- Okay. - Okay.
- That one is a bit big. - Okay.
(Happiness squeezing his finger)
(She gets ready to eat after taking off her rings.)
(Getting some noodles)
How could you go to LA...
when you're not popular?
- I haven't been to LA in my life. - You went to KCON.
That means you're famous.
(Taking a sip of the broth too)
(Getting a spoonful of rice)
She's eating well.
Do we have water?
This is so good.
So good.
I think Korean food is the best.
(I'm suited for Korean food.)
(Is she really Japanese?)
Right?
Woni, please get changed.
(Being summoned for the 2nd time)
I think they're calling me.
Go slowly.
She'll get there in five minutes.
- Keep eating. - Can you do that?
Just eat.
(Genie will protect My Star's mealtime.)
(Glancing)
It's okay. Don't be worried.
You're popular now. Don't worry.
(Joking)
(Worried look)
You're popular now. Why are you so worried?
- I guess we're popular. - You are.
How long has it been? A year?
- No. - We're not popular.
- We're not popular. - You are popular.
You're popular now.
- How could you go to LA... - You can do this much.
when you're not popular?
We're filming with Jjyu-Kkyu.
- We're popular. - Right.
- This situation itself... - Right.
(Are we popular?)
Whatever.
Did you eat enough?
We're not suddenly going to get paid less, right?
That won't happen.
You have to raise your rate for the next one...
since you're popular.
Don't make it too easy for them.
(Worried look)
I don't know what to say.
Jjyu?
Everything he said...
were pieces of advice...
that we couldn't get from the adults around us.
They have to enjoy things...
when they're doing well.
It would be nice if they keep doing well,
and if they don't, they can think about the good old days.
They'll live quietly like that.
What else can they do? That's how life is.
(Seo Jin's rational advice that threatens their innocence)
(Woni heads to get ready for her individual shoot.)
- Your slippers. - I don't need them.
- Is that all right? - Thank you.
(Running barefoot)
My stomach is about to burst.
(May and Zena head to get ready for their shoot.)
Chew it well.
I eat really well.
Of course.
You're good at using the chopsticks even though you're a foreigner.
(Of course, she is. She's Japanese.)
You can speak in Japanese.
- Would that be okay? - Yes!
Mr. Manager?
What?
- That was really... - That was...
That was English.
He couldn't understand because it was English.
She said, "Mr. Manager."
Did you say, "Mr. Manager?"
I was so nervous. I couldn't hear that.
(I couldn't hear it because I was nervous.)
I'm sorry.
This is so funny.
Japanese restaurants...
Why do they charge extra for kimchi?
(He just speaks in 0 languages now.)
- I'm curious. - He just...
He mostly spoke in Korean.
No, no.
The reason for that...
Yes.
He already doesn't understand.
(The reason for that...)
(That was too difficult for Kwang Kyu.)
How many times have you been to Japan?
Japan...
I went there once with you.
For Seo Jin's fan signing event.
- It was a fan meeting. - Fan meeting?
The venue was filled with people.
- Amazing. - It was really...
That's amazing.
There would have been so many people.
Besides Tokyo, where else have you been?
I've been everywhere.
- Really? - Yes.
(Laughing)
He had many girlfriends.
- He had many girlfriends. - Yes.
He had many girlfriends long time ago.
He had many girlfriends.
You could have stayed in Japan.
Why did you want to become an idol in Korea?
You could have debuted in Japan.
I wanted to be...
a global artist...
who is known by the whole world and even go to the US.
- Ever since you were young? - Yes.
I saw Korean artists...
win Billboard awards in the US...
and realized that the Korean market was really big.
I thought I would have a better chance to succeed.
So that's why you're studying English hard.
Right. I'm studying English.
Being fluent in English would be a plus.
I also have a sense of patriotism...
toward Japan.
I was proud...
to be Japanese.
But when I came to Korea, the trainees here...
- were very talented. - No, I'm fine.
They practiced so much.
The culture itself was different,
so I was shocked by that.
(She worked even harder to keep up with the competition.)
I wanted to reach...
a bigger world.
I decided to achieve that.
(Pursuing her dream of becoming a global artist in Korea)
(My Stars' schedule:)
(Time: 3pm, Location: Outdoor studio,)
(Details: Group ad shoot)
(Rain pours before the outdoor shoot.)
(Everyone is busy because of the sudden rain.)
It's raining a lot.
- It's a relief this was set up. - This...
(She's worried.)
(They wait under a tent until the rain stops.)
- Wait a minute. - What are you doing?
It's raining, and Kkyu and Jjyu are gone.
- We're waiting outside, - Right.
while Kkyu and Jjyu are inside. Is this okay?
They're...
(My Stars rapidly fire off their complaints.)
Are they sitting inside?
We're out here.
Their ears would probably itch...
because we're talking about them.
Right.
(Meanwhile, Kkyu, whose ears would be itching...)
Hold on.
(He's escorting Minami out after she got changed.)
My shoes!
Are these yours? Really?
- Wait. - It's okay.
Is it okay?
(He wore her shoes with the heels folded down.)
Slowly.
(He takes care of Minami with an umbrella.)
- Okay. Go! - Go!
(Rushing)
Thank you!
(My Star's scalp is precious.)
Kkyu. You can move to the rhythm.
I'm an expert at rhythms.
If it's what My Stars want,
I can do anything.
(Secretary Kkyu keeps their spirits up during the wait.)
Hold on. What's Jjyu doing when you're here?
- What's Jjyu doing? - You're out here in the rain.
He just came out.
- Jjyu! - Jjyu!
(He's caught trying to slack off.)
(Chirping and calling for Jjyu in one voice)
- Jjyu! - Jjyu! Hurry up!
(Come out quickly.)
I think Jjyu is a bit slow.
(Gasping)
(Exclaiming)
"Isn't he going to come?"
(Glancing)
(I'm sorry.)
- I think he's still... - There he is.
(Jjyu comes out with an umbrella.)
Jjyu, you're so slow.
- Ready? - Yes.
Come inside the tent.
(It's raining.)
(They wait for the rain to stop.)
Hey.
Don't you feel it?
(There are also mosquitoes.)
I think I got a mosquito bite.
Did you spray mosquito repellent?
- No. - Do you want it?
Yes, please.
Kwang Kyu, can you get me the mosquito spray?
(Here comes the mosquito repellent.)
(Because we can't let precious My Stars get bitten by mosquitoes)
- Me too. - Me too.
(Holding his breath to spray)
(Kyu the pest control only for My Stars)
(Exhaling)
I was holding my breath. I'm dizzy now.
Do you want us to spray it on you?
- What? - Do you want us to spray it on you?
Raise your arms and turn around.
Turn around.
Hey, don't do it on his face.
(Spraying the mosquito repellent on his face by accident)
Only on his body.
Hey, you just sprayed it on his face.
I'm sorry.
- You sprayed it right on my face. - I'm sorry.
Tomorrow...
I don't need it.
- Still. - I don't need it.
- We'll do it for you. - No.
The rain stopped.
Get ready for the group photo.
- Okay. - Okay.
Wait.
This way?
- Oh, thank you. - Thank you.
Thank you so much.
(Spraying the mosquito repellent to the end)
Wait. Did you spray it again?
Pretend you're playing.
Go.
(Pretending to have fun)
Okay. Good.
Keep smiling.
Keep smiling. Look cheerful.
That's good.
Enjoy it while it lasts.
They're happy because they became famous.
They couldn't be happier.
Okay.
Smile.
That's good.
- That's good. - Jjyu and Kkyu, make us smile.
- Try to look cheerful. - Make us laugh.
You can face each other.
Kkyu, do something.
He's so cute. Look at his legs.
(My Stars asked me to make them laugh.)
That's good.
(Making the girls laugh with his weird dance)
- Keep it up. - He's so funny.
He's doing his best.
(The older bestie also makes Seo Jin laugh.)
(Kwang Kyu's dance makes everyone happy.)
(Kwang Kyu made his day worthwhile.)
(Thanks to Kwang Kyu, their photos look great.)
Try to look happy. That's good.
Keep looking at the camera.
Good. Perfect. Okay.
Keep changing the pose.
(Seo Jin's monitoring.)
Eyes on the camera. Smile.
So pretty. Good job.
(The shoot never ends.)
Good job. Perfect.
(However, as the shoot continues from the morning,)
Be cheerful. Pretend to talk.
Pretend to talk. That's right.
(My Stars are getting tired.)
Smile.
Okay. Let's see.
(In fact, Minami has a cold.)
How many pictures are they taking?
Hang in there. You're almost there.
- Jjyu is here. - Jjyu is finally here.
- Jjyu. - Hang in there.
If you hurry up, it'll be done soon.
- Yes, that's right. - So hang in there.
(Seo Genie looks after them nonchalantly.)
All right.
- Jjyu is stable. - What?
- Yes. - I know.
- Okay. Smile. - What a waste.
That's good. You look great.
- Good. - Smile, so it'll be done soon.
- Good. - You know?
- Smile, and it'll be over soon. - Okay.
Smile, and it'll be over soon.
- Smile as brightly as you can. - Be cheerful.
It's all money.
(It's all about money in the end.)
- You're making money. - That's good.
- Smile. - Good. Look at the camera.
(Capitalistic advice to young girls)
- Good. - May, smile.
Eyes on the camera. That's good.
Perfect.
Smile brightly.
May, smile.
Don't cover your face with it.
- Good. - Here we go.
Make sure to show the product.
(Realistic advice from the commercial master)
Good.
(My Stars are becoming professional thanks to his capitalistic advice.)
Stretch your arms for that.
Everyone, stretch your arms.
Toward the camera.
He was so down to earth.
He actually helped me face reality.
- Hurry up, - He told us we should hurry up,
- so it'll be over soon. - so it'd be over soon.
- Smile, so it'll end soon. - Or telling us to smile,
so it'd end soon.
It's actually helpful mentally...
at work.
I liked how honest he was.
(The capitalism preacher is happy.)
We'll finish it up.
- Yes. Thank you. - Thank you.
Here we go.
That's good. Okay.
That's pretty. Perfect.
(Woni is taking pictures alone after the group photos.)
- Good. - Woni's so pretty.
- Okay. Good. - You're so pretty.
(The capitalistic advice helps her pose.)
(Every picture looks perfect.)
Good.
Perfect.
(Winking)
Good. Okay.
(Thanks to Seo Genie, she looks professional.)
- Jjyu. Kkyu. - Yes?
- What do you need? - Can you get me my bag?
Can you get me my bag?
- Sit here. - It's yellow.
Yellow.
(Exclaiming)
It's so heavy.
What do you have in your bag?
(The XXXL bag)
- What's this? Is this yours? - Yes, it's mine.
- To relieve stress? - It's my wax squishy.
- What's that? - Do you know?
In Japanese?
No.
- Wax squishy? - It's popular these days.
(It's coated with wax, and you have to break it.)
(Gen Z's stress toy)
I always carry it with me to studios.
You bring this many?
I brought more today.
- For gifts? - To share them.
To share them with you.
- With us? - Yes.
- But... - Why do you do this?
They're popular these days.
- Really? - Yes.
Why are they popular?
I saw it on TV.
You touch this to relieve stress.
I'm so excited.
- Take one each. - Okay.
(Squeezing)
- No. - No? Okay.
- You can't squeeze it like that. - Okay.
- Sorry. - I can't?
- No. - Why not?
Once you break it, it's over.
Is that it?
You have to squeeze it at the count of three.
At the count of three.
- Yes. - All together.
(The teens' world is full of mysteries.)
Squeeze them on the count of three.
- One... - How?
- Just squeeze it. - Show me.
One, two, three.
(Everyone is enjoying the wax squishies together.)
(Thrilled)
What do you think?
(Kwang Kyu's first wax squishy)
What is this?
I heard a candy breaking inside.
(What is this?)
(Grossed out)
(His eyes are shaking...)
(due to the feel in his hands.)
It doesn't exactly feel good.
- No? - You know?
- It's supposed to make you happy. - This?
Yes.
- And you play with it. - Is this right?
This is the most popular toy right now.
- How come I didn't know? - Who...
Who plays with it?
Young people.
- Really? - Yes.
(The secretaries don't understand.)
Just keep squeezing.
What do you think?
I've never heard of it before.
(Is it not fun?)
(How about the wax squishy ASMR?)
How is it?
Don't you love the sound?
I have bad hearing.
Try it on him.
I can hear it.
- I can hear it from mine. - And?
What? It doesn't exactly make me happy.
No? Then...
(Disappointed)
Just say it makes you happy.
(On eggshells)
Then try this.
- What's this? - You keep it inside the bag.
- Inside the bag? - Yes.
Why?
I should've done it with my members.
(They all find it lame.)
What happens when you do it with your members?
It exploded.
- What happens when you... - It exploded.
(He even popped it.)
(On eggshells)
- No. - No.
How hard did you squeeze it?
(My Star's wax squishy popped.)
- Really? - Maybe it's defective.
No.
- Put it in here. - What...
It's not supposed to pop, is it?
No.
- It's on my hands. - What is that?
Jjyu!
- You're too strong. - What?
What's inside?
Don't eat it.
It's so hard to pop it.
(Depressed even more)
What is this?
There's juice with that inside.
If you press them, they pop.
(Exclaiming)
Like chocolate snacks?
What do you think?
(On eggshells)
It's fun.
- This is my first time trying this. - This is interesting.
I've only seen this on YouTube.
- This is your first time? - Yes.
(Relieved)
I'll give the other one to Jjyu.
- Yes, let Jjyu try. - What?
If you pop these balls inside...
- Again? - Yes.
This is thick on the outside.
- It won't pop. - No?
No. Try it.
I saved 1 for you out of 3.
(Pop)
So?
(How does it feel?)
Am I supposed to feel good?
(Still incomprehensible)
(Seo Jin will never enjoy it.)
Yes. What?
That was awesome.
(Pop)
- That was awesome. - That was awesome?
- Is that what you like? - That was amazing just now.
- That's what I'm supposed to do. - Yes.
It's like...
I think it popped again.
Again?
(As soon as he touches it)
No.
(The wax squishy killer)
I think it's ripped. It's leaking.
- Really? - Yes.
It's leaking again.
Why does that keep happening to you?
(Let's protect May's squishies.)
- Hey. What's wrong with you? - This isn't going to work.
Something sharp poked it when I popped it.
Jjyu.
This isn't for me.
No more squishies for Jjyu.
No more squishies for you.
- You can use the ones... - You should touch it gently.
that don't pop.
Yes.
I've never seen anyone...
who pops them in just three seconds.
I should've told him...
to be careful with them.
They were detective.
- No. - You can blame him.
They weren't detective.
I've checked them.
You can buy them separately.
What is this?
A giant squishy.
(Handing a giant squishy to Kwang Kyu)
(Laughing)
Oh, my gosh.
It actually looks good.
- Go, RESCENE. - Thank you.
Yaho!
(May has a good idea.)
(Please make RESCENE more successful.)
Like building a stone tower.
Right.
I see.
- Gimbap. - Right?
(He'll even become a stone tower for My Stars.)
I should've done it with the girls.
(Woni joins the wax squishies.)
I saw it on the news...
that it's too toxic for children.
I heard the ones with the KFC mark are okay.
KFC?
- KFC is... - That's a fried chicken place.
Isn't that KS?
(Even worse)
"KFC..."
(You mean the KC mark?)
KF?
- K... - KFC?
You don't know.
KC. It's okay if it has the KC mark on it.
(She remembered.)
It's okay if it has the KC mark on it.
Don't air that, please.
- It's embarrassing. - Cut.
- Anything with the KC mark is fine. - You know what to do.
You even know how editing works.
How much is this?
It's expensive these days. Over ten dollars.
- For one? - Yes.
The one you just popped.
You'd pay over ten dollars for this?
We just lost one fried chicken.
It really is KFC.
(Failing to change the subject)
- Right? - Stop saying that.
Jjyu! Kkyu!
Why do you keep embarrassing your artist?
- You can't do that. - Seriously.
(Let me protect my youngest!)
Protect your artist.
- Artist... - Protect the artist?
We can't do that to our artists.
Have you got paid?
- No, not yet. - No?
So you need to...
save up.
If you invest in weird places...
and they go wrong,
you lose everything.
But we don't know...
anything about stocks.
You don't need to know that.
When you get paid later,
don't waste it.
Be frugal and save your money.
- Don't look for a jackpot... - I'm going to buy squishies.
- We can buy squishies. - Don't buy...
more than 3 or 4. Do you hear me?
Don't buy a dozen like this.
- Okay. - Do you hear me?
- We already bought a dozen. - Don't spend your money on weird...
Then what do you do for fun?
Me?
- Making fun of Kkyu. - Your small but definite happiness.
What's that?
(What's the small but definite happiness?)
Something that's small but definitely makes you happy.
First of all,
happiness depends on your attitude.
But if you make a lot of money, happiness automatically follows.
(But if you make a lot of money, happiness automatically follows.)
(Flustered)
It's guaranteed. You'll be happy.
- If you make money. - But is money really everything?
- I think... - It's everything.
It's everything.
I don't know yet because I haven't made any yet.
(What a lesson.)
I think Jjyu is right.
The squishies don't make him happy,
but he always looks happy.
- Is that because he's rich? - He's...
He doesn't need to find happiness with minor stuff like this.
You got it.
I was shocked because...
I thought I didn't need money...
to be happy.
Anyway, is that true?
Somebody needs to tell me.
It might not be true.
Were you happy when you moved to a bigger house?
- I was so happy. - Hey.
- Oh, right there. - See?
- My goodness. - I get it now.
- What? - This is crazy.
It was already part of your life.
You just didn't realize it.
(Capitalism is already permeating.)
You're on the right track.
- I was already enjoying it. - Of course.
You're becoming the slave of capitalism.
(She has never met any grown-up like him before.)
(How's the shoot going?)
Oh, what is this?
What's here? It's catering.
- Did they call a buffet? - What?
Did they call a buffet?
(Food prepared by the production team)
A buffet...
We've already had that.
Oh, my gosh.
Woni.
- Do you want something to eat? - I'm here because I'm hungry.
You're hungry? But you ate so much.
- You're hungry again? - Yes.
Get whatever you need.
(Grabbing zucchini jeon)
- That's a vegetable. - Only zucchini jeon?
(Staring)
They're shooting.
They have to shoot, right?
Is that how you use chopsticks?
(A strange way of using chopsticks)
You...
The way you use chopsticks...
I carry training chopsticks with me.
- For kids? - Yes.
- I'll do it. That's frustrating. - Yes. Do it for her.
Only meat? No vegetables?
- No vegetables. - What?
That's fine.
I get criticized a lot because of the way I use chopsticks.
Then you should learn.
- I'm practicing. - Yes.
You can practice while eating.
- Yes. Let's go. - Yes.
(He'll also teach her how to use chopsticks.)
(Preparing food for My Star first)
May, do you want some food too?
No, I'm good.
Eat a lot and make a lot.
How come you're not doing anything?
I'm going last.
(Trying to focus on the chopsticks)
(Watching carefully)
What are you doing?
(What are you doing?)
(Dangling)
What are you doing?
(The strangest way of using chopsticks)
Hey, you have to lean that on this finger.
(Lean the chopstick on the fourth finger.)
I think I got it, right?
- Yes, you got it. - Yes.
But I can't move them.
You need to practice that.
- How am I supposed to know? - Here.
Hold this.
Just move this.
- Does this stay still? - You should...
The fourth finger stays still.
(Keep the fourth finger still.)
Move this.
Do you see it?
- Okay. - Got it?
I think I got it.
(Leaning it on the fourth finger as she's taught)
(Staring)
No. I said you should lean it on the fourth finger.
(The chopstick man is impatient.)
Where on the fourth finger?
Lean it on the fourth finger. Is it leaning?
Yes, good. Lean that here.
- Try this. - Is this right?
- Yes. Here. - Yes.
Move this.
(He sounds quite kinder than you think.)
(What's the result of his strict training?)
Oh, you got it.
You got it. Good job.
You're a genius.
- Yes. - Good job.
You got it.
- Do you know how it works now? - You got it.
(Now she just needs to eat.)
(Eating smoothly)
Good job.
Yes.
Oishii.
By the way...
By the way, you need to keep the chopsticks balanced.
If one is too long, and the other is too short,
how are you going to grab food?
(The chopstick man is not easy to satisfy.)
Right? Try it now.
You know how to hold them at least.
Jjyu, I like that. You have to tell her every day.
Hold the chopsticks even when you're going to bed.
(Even before going to bed)
Then you can fix it.
(The chopstick man is persistent.)
Let's fix Woni and May's makeup.
Okay.
- But I just learned it. - Where?
- Yes. - You got it.
- That's good. - Good job.
(Trying what she learned)
- You got it. - You did it.
Oishii.
Try it again after the shoot.
(Strict)
- Yes. - Or I'll take the food away.
Yes, sir!
See you later.
Thank you.
(The chopstick student leaves for the shoot.)
She has to practice.
Back in the military, I held the chopsticks for a week.
Because my girlfriend criticized me.
(Because my girlfriend criticized me)
(He was more scared of his girlfriend than the commander.)
You're different from me.
I fixed it right away after I got slapped in the face.
(That's how it was back then.)
It's cold.
(Taking a break while the studio is getting ready)
It's cold...
even if you turn off the AC in hotels.
(Copying Jjyu's pose)
(Spotting May)
(Smiling)
What?
- Jjyu. - Yes?
There's a place I want to go.
Where?
We have a little bit of time.
I want to go to a gacha store.
- What? - Gacha.
Do you know gacha?
The capsules.
- I heard it's crazy now. - I want to go there.
- Yes. Totally. - Right?
But it was popular in Japan.
- Yes. - Right?
I go to Japan for that.
I heard we have what Japan doesn't have.
(May also loves gacha.)
Anything you want, we'll make it true.
- Let's go! - Let's go.
(Woni, the gacha mate, joins after her shoot.)
- Nice. - Is it nearby?
Jjyu-Kkyu is the best.
You're even coming to...
- the gacha shop with us. - For real.
Such simple pleasures give us the energy during shoots.
Totally.
Do you know any abbreviations?
- Abbreviations I know? - Yes.
I hate abbreviations.
- You do? - Yes.
Do you know our catchphrase?
- Catchphrase? - I have a catchphrase.
- What is it? - It's...
Everyone knows what it is.
- Wait. - Let me tell you. Make a thumbs up.
- Thumbs up. - Thumbs up.
Swipe your lips with it.
(They don't know what it is, but still copy her.)
Oishii!
- Oh, yeah? - Oi... What?
- Oishii. - Oh, yeah?
- Oishii. - Oishii.
But it has a dialect.
- Okay, a dialect version? - A dialect version.
(Oishii)
(A little bit of dialect in the Japanese)
A dialect version.
Oishii!
- Like so. - Oishii!
Nice.
- Go ahead. - Nice.
- Go ahead. - I can't do dialects.
- Kwang Kyu is good at dialects. - You can do mine.
- You have one too? - I do have a catchphrase.
Why does everyone have one?
(Why does a girl group have so many?)
My Genie Secretary feels great to hold.
- That's it. As for the hand... - Feels great to hold?
- Yes. I... - What's that?
- When I had seized an opportunity, - Yes?
I said, "Opportunities feel great to hold."
- That was what I said. - It feels great to hold.
That's right.
- It feels great to hold. - Yes.
My Genie Secretary feels great to hold.
(Pressing her lips together)
It feels great to hold!
(Ladies, the trends are trending too fast.)
The smell of meat feels great to hold.
The smell of meat, oishii.
(Let me give it a go.)
Salt bread, oishii!
Bean sprout and rice soup, oishii!
You're the best.
(Getting immersed in My Star's catchphrases)
Oishii!
(Spotted someone)
- Hi. - Hi.
- You're so pretty. - Oh, my gosh.
(Ran into RESCENE's fans for the first time)
Amazing.
Hi!
Hi.
(More and more people start recognizing RESCENE.)
Are they recognizing RESCENE?
This is wild.
Is RESCENE on fire?
It's RESCENE!
- It's RESCENE! - Do you know RESCENE?
- Good luck! - It's RESCENE!
(Everyone recognizes My Star.)
- Good luck! - Good luck!
(RESCENE is the best!)
- Good luck! - They know RESCENE.
- Thank you. - He recognized RESCENE.
- RESCENE. - He recognized RESCENE.
- He recognized RESCENE. - He did.
- Hi. - Hi.
- Where was it? - Right.
- It's May! - Thank you.
May is right here.
- Hi. - Hi.
Hi.
- Geoje, yaho! - Yaho!
(Even the global catchphrase, Geoje, yaho)
- Yaho? They said it. - We got a yaho.
- We heard our first yaho. - Nice.
- Yaho! - Yaho! The first yaho.
RESCENE is on fire.
(Amazed)
Honestly, I didn't really know who they were.
People know RESCENE more than I thought.
I never had the experience...
of someone suddenly recognizing us...
while walking on the streets.
Say that someone says, "It's May!"
I think, "They even know my name?"
It makes me really happy.
- What? Hey. - Is this the place?
- Is this the place? - It's amazing.
- Oh, my gosh. - Is it?
- My gosh. - What are those?
(Gen Z hotspot, gacha shop)
Oh, my gosh. How cute!
(A place where you can randomly get cute keychains and figures)
It's not the kind of place I saw in the news.
(Time: 11:30am to 6pm, Location: Studio, Details: Commercial shoot)
(Quick break: Gacha shop outing)
My gosh, how cute.
I want to do this one.
We have to change cash into coins first.
That's where we do it.
(Dedicated coin dispenser)
How many coins do you each need?
(Exchanging to gacha coins first)
Is it working?
(While Kkyu and Jjyu are exchanging coins)
(Scanning the gacha machines with hawkish eyes)
(A gacha paradise packed with adorable little goodies)
I'm playing one.
- Okay. - All right.
The game that May's been wanting to play.
London game!
It's not London, but random.
Random? Random game!
Here I go.
(May tries her first random gacha.)
(Out of the many gacha machines in the store)
Kitty.
(May chooses the long-legged Kitty.)
(She wants the Angel Kitty the most!)
Here I go.
(Will she be able to get the Angel Kitty?)
(Kwang Kyu is also nervous.)
- What is it? - Kitty.
I'll open it for you.
(Will May be lucky with her first gacha?)
(Extremely excited)
Seo Jin, help me open this.
(Please.)
(Opening the first gacha)
(It's the Kitty that May wanted!)
- It's the Kitty with wings. - I envy you.
- That's cute. - Thank you.
(Succeeded on her 1st try)
It's cute.
- Do we throw this away? - Yes.
Where are the wings?
- I don't see them. - Right here.
- What? - Cute.
- Wings. - Hey.
No, they're not. They're her hands.
- No, they are wings. - It doesn't have wings.
(Wings)
No, they are wings.
- Are these wings? - Yes, the wings are on her back.
The wings are on her back.
No!
(The oldies have a hard time understanding it.)
Do you feel fun in opening these or collecting these?
- Both. - Both?
- Do you collect these? - Yes.
The other way. I'll help.
I was over the moon when I got the Kitty with wings.
I played that gacha for that very item.
- It came out on the first try. - Nice.
They don't have many years left.
The girls don't have many years left...
to find happiness in things like that.
Right? They'll soon...
go to luxury stores.
Buying handbags and such.
(Dyeing the world with capitalism)
That's life.
- These are wings. - I'm going for one too.
(My Star goes for her next gacha.)
- One. - The wings are on her back.
I want one with wings too.
(Just like May, Woni wants the Angel Kitty.)
What's yours?
It won't open.
- What? - It won't open.
(Asking the guys to open it)
What's this?
- Here. - What is it?
I can throw away the rest, right?
- Yes. - Please throw these away.
Should I try another Kitty?
I shouldn't have tried this gacha.
(I shouldn't have tried this gacha!)
(What's wrong?)
What is it? Why'd you get such an ugly one?
How unlucky.
At least she's tinted.
You're getting the dark ones today.
(Hey, I'm Tanned Kitty, not Tinted.)
Right here. It's all crowded.
Unbelievable. She has a bunch in her pouch.
Her pouch is packed.
- What are these? - I only packed my favorites.
Is that so? You must...
- have more at home. - I do.
Ta-da.
- Do you... - You connect these.
- Do you carry this pouch around? - Yes.
She's a total child.
- Cute, aren't they? - Yes.
Are you going to put that in?
(Done playing gacha)
(Thanks to the guys, the gacha break was a success!)
Let's go. It's 55 minutes.
- We've got to go. - Let's go.
Come. Let's go.
- Goodness. RESCENE's fans are... - We should go.
- My gosh. - Amazing.
(Fans have gathered after hearing that RESCENE is here.)
(It's RESCENE!)
- My gosh. - Amazing.
Please ask if they know RESCENE.
Do you know RESCENE?
(Do you know RESCENE?)
- Yes. - Yes.
- Really? - Nice.
RESCENE...
Nobody is responding.
Go with Geoje.
Geoje...
- Yaho! - Yaho!
(Geoje, yaho!)
- Incredible. - You're the only ones...
who didn't know it.
- Is that so? - Really.
- Thank you. - Let's go.
- Geoje. - Geoje?
- Woni, you... - Try it again.
- Geoje... - Yaho!
They said, "Yaho!"
Thank you!
The fans responded with "Yaho" when the guys said "Geoje."
(Laughing)
It made me happy.
The catchphrase seems more famous than the guys right now.
That's a given.
(Charmander is happy.)
Thank you!
(Just as they're about to leave after saying bye to the fans)
This is so cute!
You're right.
It's cute. Buy it.
- Do we have time? - Just a tiny bit.
- Do we have time? - Hurry.
This right here? There are others everywhere.
- This one. - Over there.
Is this also for sale?
- "Pink House?" - Yes, that one.
This one?
- Pink House... - How much is it?
- Is it expensive? - It's 70 dollars.
Sorry?
(It's quite pricey as it's handmade with love.)
It's okay then.
- Is it 70 dollars? - Yes.
Let's get it.
- No, it's too expensive. - No, not 70 dollars.
- You should still get something. - How about matching bracelets?
Bracelets?
- No, that's too expensive. - Do you accept Apple Pay?
- Apple Pay... No. - No?
- Do you accept Samsung Pay? - I do.
She does. Make it your treat, Kwang Kyu.
- Okay. - We need to leave in ten minutes.
One Pink House.
No, don't take it down. She said...
- not to touch it. - Okay.
Not that one. It's too expensive.
No, it'll be my treat.
- No. - It's on him. Don't worry about it.
- But 70 dollars is... - Right.
- No, it's okay. - I'm buying it.
One Pink House. Choose something, May.
- Go ahead. - No, but...
I want bracelets.
How many? Buy ten.
- Get one. - Okay?
Get one?
I'll get two.
- Okay. - Okay, two.
- How's this, May? - We don't have time. Closed.
There's a discount, right?
Give me a minute.
We've got to hurry.
- It's closed. - Thank you!
- Let's have RESCENE leave first. - What should we do?
- We're going first. Let's go. - No.
- We have to go. - No! Kkyu!
- We're leaving Kkyu behind. - Abandon him.
- Really? - Kkyu simply paid for them.
What's more, Jjyu is richer.
- But Kkyu paid for them. - Exactly.
It's okay.
Let's go.
(No!)
(No! Kkyu!)
(Busy calculating the price)
I'll take 130 dollars.
One hundred and thirty dollars?
These are... Got it.
(All are handmade, thus expensive.)
The total is 130 dollars? Unbelievable.
- Goodness. Okay. - Okay.
(Spending a fortune for My Nieces)
(Laughing)
Gosh, where are they?
How can these be 130 dollars?
(An unexpected splurge)
- Jjyu is... - You're so pretty.
- Hi. - Thank you.
Good luck.
(Looking back)
- Kkyu! - Kkyu!
Yaho!
- Yaho! - Kkyu! Thank you.
Hey!
Why'd you bring up Apple Pay?
- You little... - What?
How can you mention Apple Pay in Seoul?
Thank you so much, Kkyu.
No, don't mention it. I wanted to treat you to something.
I'll wear the bracelet every day.
Okay. It was pricier than I thought.
- It was really expensive. - For real.
- Amazing. - Recall us...
whenever you see the bracelet.
- Of course. - Yes.
Trivial things are all on Kkyu.
Trivial?
They're not trivial.
But the price isn't trivial.
If you had wanted me to buy the shop, I would've done that.
Did you just hear this bully?
- Gosh. - What?
- You sure have a way with words. - Exactly.
Be careful of guys like him.
These girls don't know what capitalism is.
(The king of flexing's capitalist sales game)
Which secretary do you prefer, Jjyu or Kkyu?
(Kkyu)
How come?
He bought me something worth 70 dollars today.
(Being honest)
She's fully embracing capitalism now.
And happiness, oishii!
(Capitalism is best!)
(While My Star is slowly getting into capitalism)
(The photoshoot is nearing the end.)
Good.
Someone wants to talk to you, so go upstairs, please.
- Us? - The managers.
- Who? - A staff member.
- Us? - The commercial. Yes.
Where do we go? What is it?
(Without a clue, the secretaries make their way upstairs.)
(A mysterious guy is walking around the waiting room.)
Where? Here?
What? What is it?
(Full of suspicion)
What's going on?
- Hi. - Hi.
- Hi. - Are you the CEO?
Right, I'm...
"Hello, I Am Woni, Nice to Meet You..."
- What? - "Hello, I Am Woni,"
"Nice to Meet You..."
- It's our channel. - YouTube channel?
Yes, I'm the director who made that channel.
The voice that appears...
- in the video. - Yes.
- That's right. - Nice to meet you.
- Likewise. - Nice to meet you.
(Suddenly smiling brightly)
- Take a seat. - Okay.
(Why does the director want to talk to us?)
I have something to ask for tomorrow.
(Something to ask us?)
We...
are doing a Q and A session to celebrate...
reaching one million quite late.
The plan is to use the Gold Button as a trivet.
(The plan is to use the Gold Button as a trivet.)
What's a Gold Button?
- Once you reach one million... - You get a Gold Button...
for reaching one million.
At 100,000, you get a Silver Button.
(A symbol of reaching one million viewers...)
(and every YouTuber's dream, Gold Button)
(Receive one, and shooting an unboxing video is a must.)
(To YouTubers, the Gold Button is as valuable as a gold medal.)
(Hello, I Am Woni, Nice to Meet You.)
(2.22 million subscribers)
(My Star should've received it much earlier.)
Will it arrive tomorrow?
- No, we already have it. - You do?
Here's what's important.
The members have no idea about it.
Do the members not know they received it?
- No, they haven't seen it. - They haven't?
They might not even know what it looks like.
(Time: 3pm, Location: Outdoor studio, Details: Group ad shoot)
(After My Star's ad shoot,)
(they have a YouTube shoot scheduled for tomorrow.)
(A YouTube 1 million celebration shoot is scheduled for tomorrow.)
(My Stars think it's an ordinary Q and A session shoot.)
(The secretaries, in secret,)
(must hide the Gold Button!)
And so,
you must keep it a secret.
The members don't know the details about tomorrow's shoot.
Since it's a surprise, you want us to be careful.
You're asking us not to be obvious.
It'll be a surprise.
Thank you.
(Location: Studio, Details: YouTube shoot for "HIAW")
(A Gold Button surprise camera)
This is me.
(In My Stars and secretaries' waiting room)
You're right.
(The Gold Button surprise shoot is...)
(being prepared below the waiting room.)
(Checking the critical site from above the studio)
Everything is ready downstairs.
- Is it? - Yes.
(Let me check as well.)
Is it ready?
What a scary story.
Look.
(What Kwang Kyu is looking at attentively)
- Everyone is waiting. - Are they done?
This studio is huge.
(The cooking space to hide the Gold Button)
(The Gold Button is next to the instant noodles.)
Are you all set?
(The secretaries and My Stars are ready.)
- How pretty. - You look like a model.
A fashion model.
- It's better than earlier. - Let's go.
- Let's go. - Get on with the shoot.
- Hurry. - Do we leave now?
Let's finish it fast.
(Checking her looks, completely unaware)
Jjyu-Kkyu, can you take the blankets with you?
- Of course. - Jjyu-Kkyu, blankets.
- I'll take them with me. - Thank you.
- No problem. - Yes.
Blankets.
- Hi. - Look at the amount.
All right. Here come our princesses!
(My princesses enter the studio, yaho!)
Here come the five princesses!
(The Gold Button hiding operation begins.)
Cutie.
- All set. - Okay.
When we begin, say, "Hello, I Am Woni, Nice to Meet You..."
"has reached one million subscribers."
(Focused on the reading, completely clueless)
- All alone. - Okay.
This is just ordinary instant noodles, right?
- Yes. - That's the powder.
Do you mind explaining it?
Which one is jjajang instant noodles?
- This one. - This one is jjajang?
I cook it without draining the water, right?
(The key to the operation:)
(Instant noodles to hide the Gold Button)
Boil it for three minutes, and then, mix.
Correct.
Are Kkyu and Jjyu cooking them for us?
- Nice. - Not me.
- It's going to be good. - Fifty years of instant noodles.
(Cook Kkyu, 50 years of instant noodles)
- Kkyu. - Do you guys like...
their noodles completely cooked or slightly cooked?
- Slightly. - Slightly.
Got it.
- I'll look forward to it. - Of course.
I can use chopsticks, right?
Right?
I need chopsticks.
(After checking the instant noodles,)
(Kwang Kyu sneaks off to a private spot.)
(Moving)
Gosh. Seriously.
(After lurking around a spooky place,)
(he takes something out.)
(Looking around)
(The valuable item to check in secret is...)
This is...
(the 100,000-subscriber Silver Button.)
(The Silver Button will also be revealed today.)
(Staring)
(Kwang Kyu has had 90,000 subscribers for a year.)
I envy them. Really.
(After the Silver Button)
Gosh. Look.
(Gold Button, Kwang Kyu's dream)
Gold Button.
Kim Kwang Kyu Loves Single, one million subscribers.
(Quietly reciting his dream)
How nice it'd be.
Gosh, when will I get one?
(Heading back after putting the dream of...)
(the Gold Button aside for now)
(Placing it at its original spot)
(Thud)
(Hand of Minus is hard at work even today.)
- Let's roll. - Okay, roll camera.
"Hello, I Am Woni, Nice to Meet You..."
has reached one million subscribers.
(Starting HIAW's 1 million celebration shoot)
(1 million, yaho!)
We're going to have fun, eating instant noodles...
and chatting away.
Let's set up the instant noodles.
Okay, please set up the instant noodles.
Okay.
Instant noodles.
(Kwang Kyu starts cooking the instant noodles.)
(Starting the stopwatch)
Instant noodles!
Good luck, Kkyu!
How many is it?
What's with that?
Shouldn't you have broken them up?
No, it's jjajang.
Once it boils, the noodles will fit.
Look at Kkyu. He's built a tower.
- Kkyu. - It's a tower.
Are you sure it's okay, Kkyu?
Is that okay?
- Kkyu's instant noodle shop. - Are you okay?
You do know everyone has no trust in you, right?
Are you worried?
A little.
He's had instant noodles every day for 50 years.
- Then... - And yet, he's healthy.
We'll have faith in you.
(Trust me.)
How about the members take a seat first?
- Okay. - We'll start as soon as...
- the instant noodles are ready. - Good idea.
I bet it'll taste good.
May, don't worry.
I can't lose when it comes to instant noodles.
(With Senior Cook Eom's grim determination)
(Grab the attention with the instant noodles,)
(or the whole thing will be blown immediately.)
Gosh, it's so hot.
(It's all for the success of the surprise camera!)
You'll do what was planned while having instant noodles.
(My Stars are all seated.)
I can smell the instant noodles even with my cold.
(I can smell the instant noodles even with my cold.)
Look.
Four minutes, right?
(The Gold Button is shining in private.)
(The instant noodles are perfectly cooked!)
(The preparations are done.)
The instant noodles are done.
Okay, here we go.
Let's roll.
(The surprise camera begins.)
Gosh, that was so important.
(Here come the instant noodles.)
- Here. - Thank you.
- Here we go. - Here come the instant noodles.
A trivet.
(Trivet, cue!)
A trivet. Get them a trivet.
Let's go.
(Passing on the Gold Button)
- Thank you. - Amazing.
Trivet.
Thank you.
This one's the jjajang, right?
I guess it's not one per person.
What's this?
(Placing them on top of the Silver and Gold Buttons)
My gosh.
(Reacting with delighted notes)
- My gosh. - It looks good.
Goodness.
Holy.
Holy moly.
(For now, the Gold Button has entered successfully.)
(We won't get busted, right?)
Do we dig in?
Go ahead.
- Thank you. - We can dig in, right?
Bon appetit.
- My gosh. - I'm mixing it, okay?
Let's dig in already.
- It's so good. - I'm taking some.
(Eating the instant noodles first)
(Munching)
Oishii.
(Catchphrase in between)
(Slurping)
(Impressed)
(Thinking)
- Are they going to finish them? - Do you mind...
- I think they might finish them. - if I take one fried egg?
Will they finish it?
It's ten portions.
(Is there a reason they wouldn't?)
We need to slow down.
(Gluttony on)
(Digging in)
- Take it all. - Everything...
(My Stars have lost it on the permitted cheating day.)
It's amazing.
(The instant noodles keep going in.)
Have it with green onion kimchi and...
Are you Korean?
(A Japanese who loves green onion kimchi)
It's thick.
(Almost empty)
- It's chewy. - Right?
- Those... - Yes?
- When are they opening those? - Sorry?
When are they going to open the Gold Button?
(You're right.)
We'll begin the Q and A session for reaching one million subscribers.
Okay.
(Shall we begin the real game?)
(The Silver and Gold Buttons are still under the instant noodles.)
And so,
we'll give you the Gold Button.
- Okay. - Okay.
- Here they go. - Gold Button...
You're right.
Do you have it right now?
(The members are buzzing.)
- Guys. - It's my first time seeing one.
- Me too. - Same here.
I've never seen one before.
- I didn't know that. - Amazing.
Where is it?
- We already gave it to you. - What?
(What do you mean?)
We already gave it to you.
It must be at the company.
You got it first and hid it, right?
- Maybe not? - Get up, Woni.
You're sitting on it, right?
(Isn't it this?)
- Under the instant noodles. - What?
- Seriously? - These?
- Underneath! - Seriously?
- How could you... - As trivets?
(The girls have gone wild.)
- For real? - The pots are heavy.
Are you serious?
(A crazy idea to use the Gold Button as a trivet)
Oh, my gosh.
(Even the fans went wild.)
Why were these here?
Unbelievable.
I'm opening it.
I've only seen this in videos.
Amazing.
(Shiny)
Open it.
Hold on.
I'm jealous.
(He's serious.)
Hold on.
Let's leave a fingerprint each. What do you think?
No.
- My gosh. It's so nice. - You should wash your hands first.
The button is so pretty.
It looks good on you.
Hello, I am Woni.
(Just like the Gold Button pinned under the instant noodles,)
(their moments couldn't shine.)
I got my hair and makeup done for this.
(Until everyone discovered them,)
(My Stars were shining in silence.)
(From the sparkling footsteps that never stopped...)
(to a great light that makes everyone stop and look)
(Let's go, Charmander!)
He recognized me.
Geoje...
(Brighter days are waiting ahead for My Stars.)
They said, "Yaho!"
- Hi. - Hi.
- Really? - You're now a YouTuber...
with one million subscribers.
- A one-million-subscriber YouTuber. - How does it feel to be one?
We worked together to reach one million.
(Tearing up)
We should also get the Diamond Button.
(Kkyu is also tearing up.)
Take a look at each.
Can I hold it too?
I'd better get good energy from it.
Good idea.
Moment as an idol.
Woni, use this to check your teeth.
- You're right. - Right?
(How the 1-million-subscriber YouTuber checks her teeth)
(How cute.)
- We were RESCENE. - We were RESCENE.
- Please keep supporting us. - Please keep supporting us.
(Next schedule: A small get-together, yaho)
- Have one each. - Thank you.
This drink is delicious.
(Drinks from the secretaries for My Stars)
Great work today.
- Thank you. - Great work.
- Cheers. - Cheers.
- Cheers. - Well done.
(Cheers to My Stars for their hard work)
(Cheers to Jjyu and Kkyu for their hard work)
- It has zero calories. - Really?
Yes. Incredible, right?
We drink it every day without worries.
But then...
you can't tell it's a zero drink from the taste.
It doesn't taste like zero calories.
It's slightly bland.
- The taste... - Isn't it natural flavoring?
It tastes like 1,000 calories.
- One thousand calories? - Right?
(Capitalism on)
- It pairs with any kind of food. - Totally.
It comes in various flavors.
- It's good despite it being zero. - Yes.
I heard it was zero calories since its first release.
- Am I right? - Correct.
- How did you know? - It's well-known now.
Everyone knows about it because you promote it.
(The perfect answer)
- Nice. - As expected.
A tissue, please.
You were good...
- and really digging in. - It was good.
How can you girls eat that much?
(My Stars put on a good eating show.)
I couldn't stop myself because it was that good.
(Copying the capitalism)
(Laughing)
See that? What they say is on a higher level than ours.
Their comments are golden.
These girls are the slaves of capitalism.
- No. We're... - Did you...
- Did you see them dig in? - Right.
For the promotion,
- No. - they dug in.
- We ate it because it was good. - It was for the promotion.
We ate it because it was good.
- It was really good. - It was delicious.
Only then will the company earn money,
pay you,
and you'll receive your money.
You get to eat good food with it. That's how it is.
- Simple pleasures don't matter. - It's not oishii.
It's okane.
(Okane: Noun, Money)
I just remembered what you taught me.
- What? - Capitalism.
Capitalism?
Money is everything.
(Money is everything.)
Money is happiness.
(That's it!)
It's not oishii.
This one is a potato.
It feels good, right?
(The girls were happy with slime squishy and malatang.)
Were you happy when you moved to a bigger house?
I was so happy.
Oh, right there.
Oishii to okane.
(Awakened by the fallen secretary)
- You're on the right track. - I guess I had it pretty good.
Yes.
- Money is happiness. - It's not oishii.
- It's okane. - It's money.
(The dark capitalist instinct)
- Money. - That must be good, right?
People live for that.
- Right. - True.
You've already changed.
(Feeling proud)
Right?
Kkyu, is there anything you want to say?
What do you live for?
Once the first payment goes through,
a lot of scammers start coming after you.
Be careful.
(Tip: Watch out for scammers.)
- And... - And...
(I didn't want to learn the hard way.)
When you buy a house...
- Yes. - I love this.
Watch out for rental deposit scams.
That's right.
Don't use your registered seal without knowing what's going on.
- Right. - Okay?
Don't get a certificate of seal impression issued either.
- Make sure to check everything. - Okay.
(What are we telling the girls?)
Do you remember performing at an elementary school sports day?
- I do. - Of course, I do.
Because one of the students who was watching...
loved it so much that they cried.
- Right. - They had a light stick too.
Why did they cry?
- They knew who we were. - One of them knew.
You should perform at a bigger venue now.
- Right. - We should go to a bigger venue.
What are you going to do now?
(He suddenly sounds strict.)
(He's putting a lot of pressure on them.)
- We'll work really hard. - What?
- It won't work... - We'll work hard.
- if you touch slime squishies... - I'm sorry.
all the time.
(He talks like a true Thinker to the very end.)
- That's my small happiness, though. - It feels like you're scolding us.
- My gosh. - Sorry.
It's good to start from the bottom and work your way up.
Because it'll feel...
even more rewarding later.
People say, "Row while the tide is in."
Watching RESCENE,
I realized that they have literally...
been rowing nonstop...
toward their dreams.
And the tide came in at the perfect moment.
My Genie Secretary.
- Yaho. - Yaho.
- Yaho. - Thank you.
- You did a good job. - Thank you.
Well done.
- Thank you. - Thank you.
(Is there anything about My Star that you envy?)
(Wealth!)
(Which of you is wealthier?)
(I bet Jang Hoon is wealthier!)
You're not even trying to win.
(My star is so rich that even Young Master has to back down.)
(A billionaire)
(My Star, Seo Jang Hoon, the richest star on our show)
(Is it okay to spend up to 10,000 dollars on a get-together?)
(Yes)
Do you really spend that much on meals for everyone?
(Why did you put the building up for sale?)
(Are we finally going to find out about his 2 billion-dollar fortune?)
(And...)
(I want to see the combination of Lee Seo Jin and Seo Jang Hoon.)
(They're both such Thinkers.)
(Everyone has been waiting for this combination.)
(Seo Jin complains the most!)
(Lee Seo Jin, who is brutal with the facts)
(Jang Hoon is just as brutal!)
(Seo Jang Hoon, a master of sharp one-liners)
(Young Master...)
(versus Lord)
I'm a Thinker, but I have a warm heart.
He's a Thinker, and he's quite prickly.
(Jang Hoon wasn't like that back then.)
(This punk became a true entertainer.)
(A showdown between Thinkers)
(They have a long way to go while bickering. Will they be okay?)
(My Genie Secretary)